{
    "id": "92883daa6a664acb8220a88b1e2eda8b",
    "title": "Rewrite using modal auxiliary verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "04df77a802644a81881932bf5f31224d",
            "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It is not necessary for you to wait any longer. / You ..................... not wait any longer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "need",
                        "should",
                        "must"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are required to respect the national flag. / You ........................ respect the national flag.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was able to read when she was three. / She .................. write when she was three.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "could",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was able to solve the problem. / I ................................. solve the problem.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Perhaps she would come. / She ......................... come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are prohibited from entering my home. / You ....................... enter my house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "must",
                        "must not",
                        "need not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are allowed to go home. / You ..................... go home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "may",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is able to speak English. / She ....................... speak English.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "may",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is possible to blow glass. / Glass ......................... be blown.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "may",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is not necessary for her to pay for that call. / She .................... pay for that call.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "needs not",
                        "need not",
                        "may not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is possible for wars to break out at any time. / Wars .......................... break out at any time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "may",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I prefer to stay at home instead of going to the club. / I .......................... rather stay at home than go to the club.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "could",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}